<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Siddhant Sharma&#39;s Blog</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link>
        <description>Recent content on Siddhant Sharma&#39;s Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>siddhant385</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>My Kota Journey: Experiences, Insights, and Stories from Kota</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/p/my-kota-journey-experiences-insights-and-stories-from-kota/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/p/my-kota-journey-experiences-insights-and-stories-from-kota/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/blog/p/my-kota-journey-experiences-insights-and-stories-from-kota/mainimage.webp" alt="Featured image of post My Kota Journey: Experiences, Insights, and Stories from Kota" /&gt;&lt;!-- SEO Meta Tags --&gt;
&lt;!--&lt;title&gt;My Kota Journey: Experiences, Insights, and Stories from Kota&lt;/title&gt;--&gt;
&lt;meta name=&#34;description&#34; content=&#34;Explore my journey in Kota as a JEE aspirant. Read about the reality of Kota, the challenges, the excitement, and the lessons learned. A must-read for students aiming for success in competitive exams.&#34;&gt;
&lt;meta name=&#34;keywords&#34; content=&#34;Kota journey, JEE aspirant, Kota experiences, student life in Kota, competitive exams, coaching institutes, student stories, Kota insights, Allen Career Institute, Kota hostel life&#34;&gt;
&lt;!-- Open Graph Meta Tags for Social Media Sharing --&gt;
&lt;meta property=&#34;og:title&#34; content=&#34;My Kota Journey: Experiences, Insights, and Stories from Kota&#34;&gt;
&lt;meta property=&#34;og:description&#34; content=&#34;Explore my journey in Kota as a JEE aspirant. Read about the reality of Kota, the challenges, the excitement, and the lessons learned. A must-read for students aiming for success in competitive exams.&#34;&gt;
&lt;meta property=&#34;og:image&#34; content=&#34;mainimage.webp.jpg&#34;&gt;
&lt;meta property=&#34;og:url&#34; content=&#34;https://siddhant385.github.io/blog/&#34;&gt;
&lt;meta property=&#34;og:type&#34; content=&#34;article&#34;&gt;
&lt;!-- Twitter Card Meta Tags --&gt;
&lt;meta name=&#34;twitter:card&#34; content=&#34;summary_large_image&#34;&gt;
&lt;meta name=&#34;twitter:title&#34; content=&#34;My Kota Journey: Experiences, Insights, and Stories from Kota&#34;&gt;
&lt;meta name=&#34;twitter:description&#34; content=&#34;Explore my journey in Kota as a JEE aspirant. Read about the reality of Kota, the challenges, the excitement, and the lessons learned. A must-read for students aiming for success in competitive exams.&#34;&gt;
&lt;meta name=&#34;twitter:image&#34; content=&#34;path-to-image.jpg&#34;&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/ld+json&#34;&gt;
{
  &#34;@context&#34;: &#34;https://schema.org&#34;,
  &#34;@type&#34;: &#34;BlogPosting&#34;,
  &#34;headline&#34;: &#34;My Kota Journey: Experiences, Insights, and Stories from Kota&#34;,
  &#34;description&#34;: &#34;Explore my journey in Kota as a JEE aspirant. Read about the reality of Kota, the challenges, the excitement, and the lessons learned.&#34;,
  &#34;image&#34;: &#34;path-to-image.jpg&#34;,
  &#34;author&#34;: {
    &#34;@type&#34;: &#34;Person&#34;,
    &#34;name&#34;: &#34;Your Name&#34;
  },
  &#34;publisher&#34;: {
    &#34;@type&#34;: &#34;Organization&#34;,
    &#34;name&#34;: &#34;Your Blog Name&#34;,
    &#34;logo&#34;: {
      &#34;@type&#34;: &#34;ImageObject&#34;,
      &#34;url&#34;: &#34;path-to-logo.jpg&#34;
    }
  },
  &#34;datePublished&#34;: &#34;2024-07-31&#34;,
  &#34;dateModified&#34;: &#34;2024-07-31&#34;
}
&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;my-kota-journey&#34;&gt;My Kota Journey
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;about&#34;&gt;About
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This series comprises my story and experiences in Kota. This is the first part of the story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;photo-container&#34; style=&#34;width: 80%; max-width: 600px; margin: 20px auto; border: 2px solid #ddd; border-radius: 10px; overflow: hidden; box-shadow: 0 4px 8px rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.1);&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;image.webp&#34; alt=&#34;Kota city&#34; style=&#34;width: 100%; height: auto;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&#34;photo-caption&#34; style=&#34;padding: 10px; font-style: italic; color:red; text-align: center; background-color: #f9f9f9;&#34;&gt;Kota city&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ah, Kota! 🌟 A name that resonates with every JEE aspirant. When people think of this city, what image comes to mind? Serious students poring over books, bustling coaching centers, and an environment brimming with competition and pressure. This is what Kota means to many. 📚🏫&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But is that the whole story?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-reality&#34;&gt;What is Reality?
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reality of Kota is quite different. It&amp;rsquo;s a city like any other, filled with dreams and aspirations. Having spent almost a year here, I&amp;rsquo;ve seen the ground reality. Coaching institutes operate like educational business giants, teachers are treated like products, and top rankers are the showcases for prospective students. Some students are extremely serious, some are more relaxed, and I find myself somewhere in between, leaning slightly towards the chilled side. I&amp;rsquo;ve learned that no place is special, and no coaching can replace self-confidence and self-study. If you&amp;rsquo;re serious about your studies, you can crack any exam, anywhere, whether it&amp;rsquo;s online or offline. 💪📖&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;greed&#34;&gt;Greed?
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kota is a city driven by student demand, where local shopkeepers, from small vendors to big showrooms, aim to benefit from the student population. The greed is most noticeable in areas densely populated by students. Venturing into local markets reveals significantly lower prices for the same goods. The issue lies with students who don’t bargain, allowing shopkeepers to take advantage. Everything from room rent to basic groceries, from rubber bands to soap and shampoos, is costly here. The only reasonably priced items are books, notebooks, and study materials. 📚💸&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;drugs-suicides-and-environment&#34;&gt;Drugs, Suicides, and Environment?
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;During my time in Kota, I didn&amp;rsquo;t encounter anyone involved in drugs or other illicit activities, but I did come across mobile thieves. If you talk openly in the streets with your phone, you risk losing it. The environment is decent in terms of facilities, but if you come here alone expecting to make friends and find healthy competition, think again. The competition is toxic, and everyone is focused on their own success. You’ll rarely find anyone willing to help unless you have old friends here (I was lucky to have some 😊❤️). Making new friends is tough as everyone is so engrossed in their studies, leaving no room for social life. If you get social, you risk getting distracted by the many attractions Kota offers. This intense competition and stress contribute to the alarming rate of suicides. Emotional resilience is crucial here; if you&amp;rsquo;re emotionally weak, bring someone along to support you morally and physically. 🚫🧠&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-new-start&#34;&gt;A New Start
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;beginning-hostel-search-and-admission&#34;&gt;Beginning Hostel Search and Admission
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I arrived in Kota in April and enrolled at Allen Career Institute. The excitement of attending tuition classes for the first time was palpable. The city&amp;rsquo;s greed was evident from the moment we arrived at the Railway Station, where auto drivers were ready to overcharge us. We fell prey to this on our first day. The auto ride took 30 minutes, dropping us at the grand Sankalp building, Allen&amp;rsquo;s main office. I was awestruck by the multi-story coaching institute, resembling a castle. We went inside to secure our admission. Although our 12th-grade results were pending, the lady at the counter asked, &amp;ldquo;Are you sure you&amp;rsquo;ll get more than 75% marks?&amp;rdquo; My friends, Pushpraj and Chakku, were confident, but I had doubts due to a challenging exam environment. We completed the admission process and began our hostel search. After several attempts, we found a hostel. Despite my initial reluctance, Pushpraj, his parents, and my parents saw it as ideal. I later realized they were right. Our hostel, a mix of PG and hostel, had no strict rules. We had the freedom to come and go, bring food to our rooms, and host friends. 🏨🏰&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;photo-container&#34; style=&#34;width: 80%; max-width: 600px; margin: 20px auto; border: 2px solid #ddd; border-radius: 10px; overflow: hidden; box-shadow: 0 4px 8px rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.1);&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;Sankalp.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Description of photo&#34; style=&#34;width: 100%; height: auto;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&#34;photo-caption&#34; style=&#34;padding: 10px; font-style: italic; color:red; text-align: center; background-color: #f9f9f9;&#34;&gt;Sankalp Building src Google&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;my-room&#34;&gt;My Room
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our room was spacious, equipped with a separate washroom, AC, fan, study table, blackboard, cupboard, and beds – all in pairs for the two of us. Our parents left the same day, leaving us on our own. We began making friends and met a junior named Sameer, our neighbor. We chatted with him to get a feel of the hostel. After shopping for necessary items, we returned and rested until evening. I started wondering if Kota, notorious for suicides, had any lingering spirits in our room. Instead of feeling scared, I felt a sense of adventure. I joked to Pushpraj, &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s beat that ghost&amp;rsquo;s a**!&amp;rdquo; (As Navodayans, we had faced &amp;ldquo;ghost encounters&amp;rdquo; orchestrated by seniors trying to scare us, so we weren&amp;rsquo;t easily frightened. Navodaya is another story for another time). To our amusement, there was no ghost. Suddenly, we heard someone eavesdropping at our door. It turned out to be Aryan (another neighbor) and Sameer, attempting to scare us. We told them such antics wouldn&amp;rsquo;t work on us and urged them to try something bigger. We laughed, chatted, and then went for dinner. With excitement for the next day, we went to bed. 🛏️👻&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Attaching Some Room Images from my Gallery&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;photo-container&#34; style=&#34;width: 80%; max-width: 600px; margin: 20px auto; border: 2px solid #ddd; border-radius: 10px; overflow: hidden; box-shadow: 0 4px 8px rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.1);&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;Room.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Room.jpg&#34; style=&#34;width: 100%; height: auto;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&#34;photo-caption&#34; style=&#34;padding: 10px; font-style: italic; color:red; text-align: center; background-color: #f9f9f9;&#34;&gt;Study Table Photo from Gallery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;photo-container&#34; style=&#34;width: 80%; max-width: 600px; margin: 20px auto; border: 2px solid #ddd; border-radius: 10px; overflow: hidden; box-shadow: 0 4px 8px rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.1);&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;Room2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;My bed&#34; style=&#34;width: 100%; height: auto;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&#34;photo-caption&#34; style=&#34;padding: 10px; font-style: italic; color:red; text-align: center; background-color: #f9f9f9;&#34;&gt;Bed again from gallery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;photo-container&#34; style=&#34;width: 80%; max-width: 600px; margin: 20px auto; border: 2px solid #ddd; border-radius: 10px; overflow: hidden; box-shadow: 0 4px 8px rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.1);&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;Room3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Description of photo&#34; style=&#34;width: 100%; height: auto;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&#34;photo-caption&#34; style=&#34;padding: 10px; font-style: italic; color:red; text-align: center; background-color: #f9f9f9;&#34;&gt;Me and My Friend Pussu src Mobile Gallery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;a-new-day&#34;&gt;A New Day
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next day began with a mix of seriousness and curiosity. We were in a new world, unfamiliar with the coaching culture. How we navigated this new environment and what challenges we faced, I’ll share in the next part of my journey. Until then, goodbye! 🌞✨&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;images&#34;&gt;Images
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If my any friend wants more photos please click below and personally ask me for permission as it is locked for obvious purposes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;My journey in Kota has been a rollercoaster of emotions, experiences, and lessons. From initial excitement to harsh realities, it has been a path of self-discovery and growth. Remember, no place is inherently special, and no coaching institute can replace self-confidence and self-study. 🚀📚&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;feedback&#34;&gt;Feedback
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I would love to hear your feedback! Please share your thoughts, suggestions, and any mistakes you noticed. Your feedback is invaluable and helps me improve. Let&amp;rsquo;s make this journey interactive and engaging together! 🌟✍️&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for visiting my blog! I hope you find my posts interesting and informative. Feel free to connect with me on GitHub, Instagram, or via email. Your feedback and suggestions are always welcome. Stay tuned for more updates!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;display: flex; gap: 10px;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.github.com/siddhant385&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/91/Octicons-mark-github.svg&#34; alt=&#34;GitHub&#34; width=&#34;30&#34; height=&#34;30&#34;&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/s.i.d385&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a5/Instagram_icon.png&#34; alt=&#34;Instagram&#34; width=&#34;30&#34; height=&#34;30&#34;&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:your-email@example.com&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/4/4e/Mail_%28iOS%29.svg/640px-Mail_%28iOS%29.svg.png&#34; alt=&#34;Email&#34; width=&#34;30&#34; height=&#34;30&#34;&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://some.tm.me&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Telegram_logo.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Telegram&#34; width=&#34;30&#34; height=&#34;30&#34;&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- Templates for adding photos --&gt;
&lt;!-- 
&lt;div class=&#34;photo-container&#34; style=&#34;width: 80%; max-width: 600px; margin: 20px auto; border: 2px solid #ddd; border-radius: 10px; overflow: hidden; box-shadow: 0 4px 8px rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.1);&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;path-to-photo.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Description of photo&#34; style=&#34;width: 100%; height: auto;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&#34;photo-caption&#34; style=&#34;padding: 10px; font-style: italic; text-align: center; background-color: #f9f9f9;&#34;&gt;Caption for the photo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

--&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Flask-Phishing</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/p/flask-phishing/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/p/flask-phishing/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/blog/p/flask-phishing/image.jpeg" alt="Featured image of post Flask-Phishing" /&gt;&lt;h1 id=&#34;flask-phishing&#34;&gt;Flask-Phishing
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey there, fellow tech adventurers! 🎉 Ready to dive into the sneaky world of phishing? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry; this is all in good fun and education. Today, we’re going to explore a Python Flask phishing framework. Grab your virtual trench coat and magnifying glass, and let’s go!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phishing-the-internets-dark-alley-&#34;&gt;Phishing: The Internet&amp;rsquo;s Dark Alley 🕵️‍♂️
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Phishing is a major problem because there really is no patch for human stupidity.&amp;rdquo; - Mike Danseglio&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-on-earth-is-phishing-&#34;&gt;What on Earth is Phishing? 🤔
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine getting an email from your favorite pizza place offering free pizza for a year. You click the link, and boom! Your personal info is stolen. Phishing is like that—bad guys pretending to be someone you trust to steal your information. Sneaky, huh?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phishing is a sneaky trick where bad guys pretend to be someone you know online to steal your personal info. Imagine a wolf in sheep&amp;rsquo;s clothing, but the sheep is your favorite website. The site looks legit but is made to trick you. Always check twice before entering your info!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;so-why-should-i-care-&#34;&gt;So, Why Should I Care? 🤷‍♀️
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowing about phishing is crucial because it shows just how easy it is to fall for these tricks. But here’s the twist: we’re going to use this knowledge for good. I’ll show you how to set up a phishing site (purely for educational purposes, of course).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;: This tool is for ethical hackers only. If you&amp;rsquo;re not one of those, please go back to watching cat videos. 😸 We’re not responsible if you turn into a cyber villain. Use at your own risk, and remember, your mom was right about talking to strangers online. 🚫&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-makes-this-tool-special-&#34;&gt;What Makes This Tool Special? 🎉
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flask-Powered&lt;/strong&gt;: Deploy it on the web with ease.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No Port Forwarding&lt;/strong&gt;: Forget the hassle of port forwarding or ngrok.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User-Friendly&lt;/strong&gt;: Simple web interface that even your grandma could use (probably).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accessible&lt;/strong&gt;: Just need the internet and a web browser.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;installation-on-webhosting-&#34;&gt;Installation on Webhosting 🌐
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Requirements: Internet and a device (laptop recommended, but you can try your luck with a mobile phone).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deployment Platform: We&amp;rsquo;ll use PythonAnywhere.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-by-step-guide-&#34;&gt;Step-by-Step Guide 🚀
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create an Account&lt;/strong&gt;: Sign up on PythonAnywhere. Yes, you know how to create an account. 🙄&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dashboard Navigation&lt;/strong&gt;: Head to the dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Open a New Console&lt;/strong&gt;: Click on &amp;lsquo;New Console&amp;rsquo; and select &amp;lsquo;Bash&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clone the Repository&lt;/strong&gt;: Enter &lt;code&gt;git clone https://github.com/siddhant385/flask-phishing&lt;/code&gt; in the console.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Navigate to Directory&lt;/strong&gt;: Type &lt;code&gt;cd flask-phishing&lt;/code&gt; in the console&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Install Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;: Run &lt;code&gt;pip install -r requirements.txt.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Open Web Tab&lt;/strong&gt;: Go back to the dashboard and click on &amp;lsquo;Web&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;1.png&#34; alt=&#34;1.png&#34; width=&#34;800&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;8&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add New Web App&lt;/strong&gt;: Click on &amp;lsquo;Add new web app&amp;rsquo; and select &amp;lsquo;Flask&amp;rsquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;2.png&#34; alt=&#34;1.png&#34; width=&#34;800&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next Step&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;3.png&#34; alt=&#34;1.png&#34; width=&#34;800&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next Step&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;4.png&#34; alt=&#34;1.png&#34; width=&#34;800&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next Step&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;5.png&#34; alt=&#34;1.png&#34; width=&#34;800&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;!-- Add more images as needed --&gt;
 &lt;!-- 2.png --&gt;
&lt;!-- 3.png --&gt;
&lt;!-- 4.png --&gt;
&lt;!-- 5.png --&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;9&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Configure Path&lt;/strong&gt;: Enter the path to your main script, e.g., &lt;strong&gt;/home/yourusername/flask-phishing/main.py.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;6.png&#34; alt=&#34;6.png&#34; width=&#34;800&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;10&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After you have clicked next a web dashboard will be opened scroll down and then click go to directory of Source code as given in picture below&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;7.png&#34; alt=&#34;7.png&#34; width=&#34;800&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;11&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Now click on main.py&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;8.png&#34; alt=&#34;8.png&#34; width=&#34;800&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;12&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open a new tab and open this &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://github.com/siddhant385/flask-phishing/blob/main/main.py&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;url&lt;/a&gt; on your new tab and click copy button as shown in the picture
Url is : &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://github.com/siddhant385/flask-phishing/blob/main/main.py&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://github.com/siddhant385/flask-phishing/blob/main/main.py&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;9.png&#34; alt=&#34;9.png&#34; width=&#34;800&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;13&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After you have copied the code remove all the previous code written in the main.py and paste copied code there and click on save button&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;10.png&#34; alt=&#34;10.png&#34; width=&#34;800&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;14&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reload Your Site&lt;/strong&gt;: Click on &amp;lsquo;Reload&amp;rsquo; on the PythonAnywhere dashboard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;11.png&#34; alt=&#34;11.png&#34; width=&#34;800&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;15&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Access Your Site&lt;/strong&gt;: Go to yourusername.pythonanywhere.com. Use default credentials &lt;strong&gt;admin&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;root&lt;/strong&gt; to log in, then change them immediately.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;12.png&#34; alt=&#34;12.png&#34; width=&#34;800&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
- You will be redirected to a new page click on config tab and change your username and password. Hence you are good to go
&lt;h3 id=&#34;congrats-&#34;&gt;Congrats! 🎉
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;You have successfully hosted your phishing site!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;aftermath&#34;&gt;Aftermath🎭
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create a Telegram Bot: Send usernames and passwords directly to your Telegram bot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Send Links: Share links to teach others about phishing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;View Trapped Data: Check the DATA tab for captured info.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute: Help improve the tool.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Star the Repo: Show your support for the author! 🌟&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;prevention-tips-&#34;&gt;Prevention Tips 🚨
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid unexpected links or attachments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hover over links to check URLs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enable 2FA for extra security.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep your system, browser, and antivirus updated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, there you have it, the lowdown on phishing. It&amp;rsquo;s like those annoying telemarketers but way sneakier. Be smart, stay alert, and don&amp;rsquo;t click on everything you see. If it sounds too good to be true, it probably is. When in doubt, ask a friend, parent, or teacher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, your online life is like your room: keep the doors locked and don&amp;rsquo;t let just anyone in. 🛡️&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Write your thoughts in the comments below!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for visiting my blog! I hope you find my posts interesting and informative. Feel free to connect with me on GitHub, Instagram, or via email. Your feedback and suggestions are always welcome. Stay tuned for more updates!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;display: flex; gap: 10px;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.github.com/siddhant385&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/91/Octicons-mark-github.svg&#34; alt=&#34;GitHub&#34; width=&#34;30&#34; height=&#34;30&#34;&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/s.i.d385&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a5/Instagram_icon.png&#34; alt=&#34;Instagram&#34; width=&#34;30&#34; height=&#34;30&#34;&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:your-email@example.com&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/4/4e/Mail_%28iOS%29.svg/640px-Mail_%28iOS%29.svg.png&#34; alt=&#34;Email&#34; width=&#34;30&#34; height=&#34;30&#34;&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://some.tm.me&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Telegram_logo.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Telegram&#34; width=&#34;30&#34; height=&#34;30&#34;&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
```
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>About</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/about/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/about/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About Me
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div align=&#34;center&#34; style=&#34;padding:50px;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src = &#34;profile.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Profile Photo&#34; width=&#34;200&#34; height=&#34;200&#34; style=&#34;border-radius:30%;&#34;&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
Hi, I&#39;m Siddhant Sharma, a passionate coder and technology enthusiast. I recently passed highschools from Jawahar Navodaya Vidyalaya, Badwara Katni, and am currently planning my undergraduate studies. My interests span across coding, traveling, exploring new technologies, and creating innovative solutions. I&#39;m always eager to learn new things and take on challenging projects.
&lt;h2 id=&#34;siddhant-sharma&#34;&gt;Siddhant Sharma
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;education&#34;&gt;Education
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High School&lt;/strong&gt;: Jawahar Navodaya Vidyalaya, Badwara Katni&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Current Status&lt;/strong&gt;: Planning for undergraduate studies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;hobbies&#34;&gt;Hobbies
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Coding&lt;/strong&gt;: I love to program and solve challenging problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traveling&lt;/strong&gt;: Exploring new places and cultures is my passion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Typing&lt;/strong&gt;: I love to challenge in &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;%27https://play.typeracer.com%27&#34; &gt;Typeracer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technology&lt;/strong&gt;: I enjoy exploring new technologies and staying updated with the latest trends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Creativity&lt;/strong&gt;: I have a knack for creating something unique and innovative.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;github-stats&#34;&gt;GitHub Stats
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://github-readme-stats.vercel.app/api?username=siddhant385&amp;show_icons=true&amp;theme=radical&#34; alt=&#34;GitHub Stats&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;typeracer-stats&#34;&gt;TypeRacer Stats
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://data.typeracer.com/pit/profile?user=indianracer385&amp;ref=badge&#34; target=&#34;_top&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://data.typeracer.com/misc/badge?user=indianracer385&#34; border=&#34;0&#34; alt=&#34;TypeRacer.com scorecard for user indianracer385&#34;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;contact-me&#34;&gt;Contact Me
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;display: flex; gap: 10px;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.github.com/siddhant385&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/91/Octicons-mark-github.svg&#34; alt=&#34;GitHub&#34; width=&#34;30&#34; height=&#34;30&#34;&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/s.i.d385&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a5/Instagram_icon.png&#34; alt=&#34;Instagram&#34; width=&#34;30&#34; height=&#34;30&#34;&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:ssiddhant385@gmail.com&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4e/Mail_Icon.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Email&#34; width=&#34;30&#34; height=&#34;30&#34;&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://some.tm.me&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Telegram_logo.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Telegram&#34; width=&#34;30&#34; height=&#34;30&#34;&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>My First Blog</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/p/my-first-blog/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/p/my-first-blog/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/blog/p/my-first-blog/image.png" alt="Featured image of post My First Blog" /&gt;&lt;h1 id=&#34;welcome-to-my-blog-&#34;&gt;Welcome to My Blog 🎉
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone! 👋 My name is Siddhant Sharma, and I’m thrilled to welcome you to my blog. I recently completed my highschool from Jawahar Navodaya Vidyalaya, Badwara Katni, and am currently planning my undergraduate studies. This blog is my space to share my journey, experiences, and passions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://via.placeholder.com/800x400.png?text=Welcome&amp;#43;to&amp;#43;My&amp;#43;Blog&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Welcome Image&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-journey-into-coding-&#34;&gt;My Journey into Coding 💻
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ever since I was introduced to coding, I’ve been fascinated by the endless possibilities it offers. From solving challenging problems to creating innovative solutions, coding has become an integral part of my life. I started with basic programming languages and gradually moved on to more complex projects. Each step of the way has been both challenging and rewarding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;my-first-project-hello-world-&#34;&gt;My First Project: Hello World 🌍
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of my first projects was the classic &amp;ldquo;Hello World&amp;rdquo; program. It may seem simple, but it marked the beginning of an exciting journey into the world of coding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/05/HelloWorld_with_JavaScript.png&#34; alt=&#34;Hello World Program&#34; width=&#34;600&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;my-hobbies-and-interests-&#34;&gt;My Hobbies and Interests 🌟
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apart from coding, I have a deep love for traveling. ✈️ Exploring new places and cultures not only enriches my life but also fuels my creativity. I also enjoy keeping up with the latest technological advancements and experimenting with new tools and frameworks. Creating something unique, whether it&amp;rsquo;s a piece of code or a personal project, gives me immense satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;my-educational-path-&#34;&gt;My Educational Path 🎓
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I completed my high school education at Jawahar Navodaya Vidyalaya, Badwara Katni. The supportive environment and excellent faculty there played a significant role in shaping my academic journey. Now, as I plan my undergraduate studies, I’m excited about the new learning opportunities and experiences that lie ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-i-love-coding-&#34;&gt;Why I Love Coding 💖
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coding is not just a skill but a passion for me. It’s amazing how a few lines of code can transform ideas into reality. My favorite programming languages include Python and JavaScript, and I’ve worked on several projects that I’m proud of. One such project is a personal website I built from scratch, which taught me a lot about web development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;github-stats-&#34;&gt;GitHub Stats 📊
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out my GitHub stats to see some of the projects I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://github-readme-stats.vercel.app/api?username=siddhant385&amp;show_icons=true&amp;theme=radical&#34; alt=&#34;GitHub Stats&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;future-plans-and-aspirations-&#34;&gt;Future Plans and Aspirations 🚀
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead, I have several goals. In the short term, I aim to master advanced algorithms and data structures. In the long run, I aspire to become a full-stack developer and contribute to open-source projects. I’m particularly interested in artificial intelligence and look forward to diving deeper into it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;call-to-action-&#34;&gt;Call to Action 📬
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for visiting my blog! I hope you find my posts interesting and informative. Feel free to connect with me on GitHub, Instagram, or via email at &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;mailto:ssiddhant385@gmail.com&#34; &gt;ssiddhant385@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;. Your feedback and suggestions are always welcome. Stay tuned for more updates!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;display: flex; gap: 10px;&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.github.com/siddhant385&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/91/Octicons-mark-github.svg&#34; alt=&#34;GitHub&#34; width=&#34;30&#34; height=&#34;30&#34;&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/s.i.d385&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a5/Instagram_icon.png&#34; alt=&#34;Instagram&#34; width=&#34;30&#34; height=&#34;30&#34;&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:ssiddhant385@gmail.com&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4e/Mail_Icon.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Email&#34; width=&#34;30&#34; height=&#34;30&#34;&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://some.tm.me&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Telegram_logo.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Telegram&#34; width=&#34;30&#34; height=&#34;30&#34;&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
```
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archives</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/archives/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/archives/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Links</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/links/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/links/</guid>
        <description>&lt;!-- To use this feature, add `links` section to frontmatter.

This page&#39;s frontmatter:

```yaml
links:
  - title: GitHub
    description: GitHub is the world&#39;s largest software development platform.
    website: https://github.com
    image: https://github.githubassets.com/images/modules/logos_page/GitHub-Mark.png
  - title: TypeScript
    description: TypeScript is a typed superset of JavaScript that compiles to plain JavaScript.
    website: https://www.typescriptlang.org
    image: ts-logo-128.jpg
```

`image` field accepts both local and external images. --&gt;</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Search</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/search/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/search/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
